Guide to the Kevin Roche John Dinkeloo and Associates Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Kevin Roche John Dinkeloo and Associates records
1964-2010
MS 1884
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
403.92
(665 boxes)
The papers are comprised of drawings, photographs, correspondence, specifications, and publicity materials generated by Kevin Roche John Dinkeloo and Associates in the process of designing buildings, both built and unbuilt. Major projects include the New Haven Veterans Memorial Coliseum, the Oakland Museum, the Knights of Columbus Headquarters in New Haven, Connecticut, and several projects in New York City, including the Ford Foundation Headquarters, the United Nations Plaza, and the Central Park Zoo. Also included are interviews conducted by Susan O'Keefe with Kevin Roche and others, notes and bibliographic index cards.
Kevin Roche, John Dinkeloo and Associates
Arrangement
The papers are arranged by job number. Please consult the project index to access individual boxes. The addition is arranged by topic.
Conditions Governing Access
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Kevin Roche, 2007-2013 and 2015-2016; Will Miller, 2010; Pelli Clarke Pelli Architects, 2011, ASSA ABLOY, 2011.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Other Finding Aids
For a list of projects and the boxes in which project materials are located, please consult the Project Index.
Biographical / Historical
Kevin Roche John Dinkeloo and Associates in Hamden, Connecticut is a direct outgrowth of Eero Saarinen and Associates, which was originally established in 1950. When Eero Saarinen died in September 1961, the practice was taken over by Kevin Roche and John Dinkeloo with Kevin Roche resolving the remaining design issues of the twelve major projects on which Mr. Saarinen had been working at the time of his death. These included the Dulles International Airport, the St. Louis Gateway Arch, and the CBS Headquarters in New York. In 1966 the firm became Kevin Roche John Dinkeloo and Associates (KRJDA).
KRJDA has completed over 200 projects throughout the United States, Europe, and Asia. Kevin Roche, recipient of the Pritzker Prize in 1982, has designed a variety of institutional and corporate projects including 38 corporate headquarters, three hotel/apartment buildings, eight museums, numerous research facilities, theaters, schools, factories, performing arts centers, houses and the Central Park Zoo in New York. Since 1967, he has been the architect for the master plan and expansion of the Metropolitan Museum of Art in New York, designing all of its new wings and installing many of its collections. Source: Kevin Roche John Dinkeloo and Associates
Scope and Contents
The papers are comprised of drawings, photographs, correspondence, specifications, and publicity materials generated by Kevin Roche John Dinkeloo and Associates in the process of designing buildings, both built and unbuilt. Major projects include the New Haven Veterans Memorial Coliseum, the Oakland Museum, the Knights of Columbus Headquarters in New Haven, Connecticut, and several projects in New York City, including the Ford Foundation Headquarters, the United Nations Plaza, and the Central Park Zoo. The 2012-M-042 addition to the papers consist of interviews conducted by Susan O'Keefe with Kevin Roche and others, notes and bibliographic index cards.
List of projects in collection
6601 Aetna Life and Casualty Computer Headquarters
6309 Air Force Museum
9911 Banco Santander Central Hispano "Ciudad Grupo Santander"
8302 Bouygues World Headquarters
8001 Central Park Zoo
6804 Church Street Plaza
6703 College Life Insurance Company of America Headquarters
6010 Columbia Broadcasting System Headquarters
6305 Concordia Senior College
7904 Conoco Inc. Petroleum Headquarters
9408 Cummins / Fleetguard Filter Company Ltd
6311, 6316, 7802 Cummins Engine Company, Components Plant, Darlington
7709 Cummins Engine Company, Headquarters
7003, 9102 Cummins Engine Company, Sub-Assembly Plant, Walesboro
9403 Cummins Engine Company, Columbus Engine Plant
6512 Cummins Modification Facility
9402 Cummins/Tata Cummins Private LImited, Jamshedpur, India
7501 Deere and Company Headquarters - West Office Building
6402 Deere and Company Administrative Center
8105 Denver Block I Development
8004 EF Hutton - 51 West 52nd Street, New York
7701 Exxon Chemical Company Headquarters
6902 Federal Reserve Bank of New York
7203 Fiat World Headquarters
6312 Ford Foundation Headquarters
7704 General Foods Corporation Headquarters
6605x01 Harlem River - Turtle Bay
6903 IBM Computer Technology Museum
6106 IBM Pavilion - NY World's Fair 1964-1965
6905 IBM Radio Tracer Laboratory
6701 Institute for Advanced Study, Princeton University
6604 International Institute for the Study of Human Reproduction, Columbia University
6606 Irwin Union Bank and Trust Company
79-- Jefferson National Expansion Memorial
8101 John Deere Computer Center
7908 John Deere Educational Center
7803 John Deere Financial Services Headquarters
7302 Kentucky Power Company Headquarters
No# Kevin Roche John Dinkeloo and Associates 1962-1975 [Book by Yukio Futagawa]
6502 Knights of Columbus Headquarters
6704 Metropolitan Museum of Art
8002 Metropolitan Museum of Art, Lila Acheson Wallace Wing for 20th Century Art (Southwest Wing)
0015 Metropolitan Museum of Art, The Ruth and Harold D. Uris Center for Education, Phase I and II
8402 Metropolitan Museum of Art, New Japanese Galleries
9301 Metropolitan Museum of Art, Later Chinese Galleries
6704x55 Metropolitan Museum of Art, Andre Meyer Galleries
9206 9313 0016 Metropolitan Museum of Art, Greek and Roman Courtyard, Greek and Roman, Greek & Roman Wing Phase IV
6704x01 Metropolitan Museum of Art, Robert Lehman Wing
6704x03 Metropolitan Museum of Art, Temple of Dendur in the Sackler Wing
6704x09 6704x39 Metropolitan Museum of Art, Egyptian Wing, Phase I, II and III
6704x15 Metropolitan Museum of Art, American Wing with the Charles Engelhard Court
7705 Metropolitan Museum of Art, Astor Court
8502 Metropolitan Museum of Art, European Sculpture and Decorative Arts Wing & the Carroll & Milton Petrie European Sculpt Ct
6704x10 Metropolitan Museum of Art, Michael C. Rockefeller Wing for the Arts of Africa, Oceania and the Americas
9007 Millenia Singapore Office Buildings & Hotel
7903 Miller, J. Irwin and Xenia S. Residence
6406 National Center for Higher Education
6603 National Fisheries Center and Aquarium
6211 Neiman-Marcus Department Store
6509 New Haven Coliseum
79-- New York Historical Society
6104 Oakland Museum
1968 Orangery (Irwin Miller Pavilion)
7201 People's Bank, Indiana and Michigan Electric Company, Fort Wayne, Indiana
1971 Philadelphia Bicentennial
6508 Power Center for the Performing Arts, University of Michigan
6602 Resident College, Vassar College
6202 Richard C. Lee High School
7006 Richardson-Vicks, Inc. Headquarters
6214 Rochester Institute of Technology
7101 Royal Bank of Canada, Office Complex Proposal
7602 Texas Christian University, Moudy Visual Arts & Communications Building
6307 Trans World Airlines
7605 Union Carbide Corporation World Headquarters
6904 United Nations Development Corporation, United Nations Plaza Office and Apartment/Hotel Phase I
6510 United States Post Office
7707 United States Embassy London
5504 University of Chicago, Women's Residence Hall
5504 6511 7303 University of Chicago, Law School
6401 University of Massachusetts, Fine Arts Center
6513 Wesleyan University, Creative Arts Center
6313 Women's Resident Colleges, University of Pennsylvania
7005 Worcester County National Bank (7005 final design / 6802 original design)
Architecture -- United States -- History -- 20th Century; Dinkeloo, John G. (John Gerard), 1918-1981; Roche, Kevin, 1922-; Kevin Roche, John Dinkeloo and Associates
- Project Records, 1964-2010
  Other Finding Aids
  For a list of projects and the boxes in which project materials are located, please consult the Project Index.
  - Publications List - Index of Articles, 2010 (Box 372)
    Scope and Contents
    Job number: 5543
  - KRJDA Office Paint Chips (Box 579)
  - John G. Dinkeloo Personal Papers, 1957-1981
    - Correspondence (Box 363–369)
  - Kevin Roche John Dinkeloo and Associates 1962-1975 Book by Yukio Futagawa
    - Correspondence (Box 121, Box 123)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 122)
  - Interview with Kevin Roche by Suzanne O'Keefe, 1983-1984
  - Deere and Company Administrative Center, 1964
    Job number: 5609
    Job location: Moline, IL
    Project type: Headquarters
  - Columbia Broadcasting System Headquarters, 1965
    Job number: 6010
    Job location: New York, NY
    - Correspondence (Box 343)
    - Specifications (Box 343)
  - Oakland Museum, 1968
    Job number: 6104
    Job location: Oakland, CA
    Project type: Museum
    - Correspondence (Box 90)
    - Specifications (Box 89)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 91–92)
    - Slides (Box 92)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 93)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 96, Box 96A, Box 97, Box 99, Box 99A)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 95)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 96, Box 96A, Box 98)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 95–96, Box 96A)
  - IBM Pavilion - NY World's Fair 1964-1965
    Job number: 6106
    Job location: Flushing Meadows Park, Queens, NY
    Project type: Exhibition
    - Correspondence (Box 2–3)
    - Specifications (Box 23)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 2)
    - Slides (Box 2)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 4)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 5–7, Box 9, Box 11, Box 11A)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 11)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 8–10)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 8–9, Box 11, Box 11A)
  - Richard C. Lee High School, 1967
    Job number: 6202
    Job location: New Haven, CT
    Project type: Education
    - Specifications (Box 23)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 24)
    - Slides (Box 24)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 1)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 15, Box 15A, Box 16)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 15–16)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 12–16)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 15, Box 15A, Box 16)
  - Neiman-Marcus Department Store, 1965
    Job number: 6211
    Job location: Dallas, TX
    Project type: Retail
    - Correspondence (Box 174)
    - Specifications (Box 174)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 174)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 173)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 175–177, Box 177A)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 177)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 176–177, Box 177A, Box 178)
  - Rochester Institute of Technology, 1969
    Job number: 6214
    Job location: Rochester, NY
    - Correspondence (Box 144)
    - Specifications (Box 144–145)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 144)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 146)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 147–149, Box 202)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 147–149, Box 151)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 149–153)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 153)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record (Box 150)
  - Concordia Senior College
    Job number: 6305
    Job location: Fort Wayne, IN
    - Contracts (Box 218)
    - Specifications (Box 218)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 272)
  - Air Force Museum
    Job number: 6309
    Job location: Dayton, OH
    - Correspondence (Box 116–117)
    - Contracts (Box 116)
    - Specifications (Box 117)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 116)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 115)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 118)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 118)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 119–120)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 119)
  - Cummins Engine Company, Components Plant, Darlington (Chrysler-Cummins), 1965
    Job number: 6311 6316 7802
    Job location: Darlington, England
    Project type: Industrial
    - Correspondence (Box 382–383)
    - Specifications (Box 382)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 382)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 257)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 392–393)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 392–393, Box 399–400)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 392–393, Box 399–400)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 392–393)
  - The Ford Foundation Headquarters, 1968
    Job number: 6312
    - Correspondence (Box 224, Box 247–248, Box 460)
    - Specifications (Box 224)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 247–248)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 104–105)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 261–265, Box 267, Box 534–540, Box 580)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 265, Box 268, Box 270, Box 534–540)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 266, Box 269–271)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 267)
  - Women's Resident Colleges, University of Pennsylvania
    Job number: 6313
    Job location: Philadelphia, PA
    - Correspondence (Box 181)
    - Specifications (Box 181)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 181)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 180)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 185–188)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 183–184, Box 188)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 182, Box 189–190)
  - University of Massachusetts, Fine Arts Center, 1974
    Job number: 6401
    Job location: Amherst, MA
    Project type: Fine Arts Center
    - Correspondence (Box 62)
    - Specifications (Box 62)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 63)
    - Slides (Box 63)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 61)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 64)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 64, Box 68–71)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 65–67)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 64, Box 67, Box 69–71)
  - Deere and Company Administrative Center, 1964
    Job number: 6402
    - Specifications (Box 325)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 328–329)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 328–329)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 330)
  - National Center for Higher Education
    Job number: 6406
    Job location: Washington, D.C.
    - Correspondence (Box 138)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 138)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 134)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 135–136)
  - Knights of Columbus Headquarters, 1969
    Job number: 6502
    - Correspondence (Box 40–45, Box 467, Box 490–491)
    - Specifications (Box 45)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 40)
    - Slides (Box 40)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 77–78)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 56–57, Box 57A, Box 60)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 55, Box 57)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 55, Box 58–60)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 55, Box 58)
  - Power Center for the Performing Arts, University of Michigan, 1971
    Job number: 6508
    Job location: Ann Arbor, MI
    - Correspondence (Box 154)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 154)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 172)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 169–171, Box 542)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 169–171, Box 542)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 168–169)
  - New Haven Coliseum, 1972
    Job number: 6509
    Project type: Arena
    - Correspondence (Box 27–29)
    - Specifications (Box 26)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 25)
    - Slides (Box 25)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 75–76)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 19–20, Box 142)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 21–22)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 17–18)
  - United States Post Office, 1969
    Job number: 6510
    Job location: Columbus, IN
    Project type: Government
    - Correspondence (Box 127)
    - Contracts (Box 127)
    - Specifications (Box 127)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 133)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 130)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 128–131)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 129–131)
    - Drawings: As-Built/Record (Box 129–131)
  - Cummins Modification Facility
    Job number: 6512
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 394)
  - Wesleyan University, Creative Arts Center, 1973
    Job number: 6513
    Job location: Middletown, CT
    - Correspondence (Box 74, Folder 5, Box 489)
    - Specifications (Box 74)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 74)
    - Slides (Box 74)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 73)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 79–81, Box 84–86)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 82–83)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 79, Box 86–87)
  - Aetna Life and Casualty Computer Headquarters, 1972
    Job number: 6601
    Job location: Hartford, CT
    - Correspondence (Box 201–203, Box 343)
    - Specifications (Box 202–203)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 202)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 201)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 208–211)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 205–209)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 204–207)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 205, Box 207)
  - Resident College, Vassar College
    Job number: 6602
    Job location: Poughkeepsie, NY
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 179)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 179)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 179)
  - National Fisheries Center and Aquarium
    Job number: 6603
    Project type: Aquarium
    - Correspondence (Box 31, Box 88, Box 577)
    - Contracts (Box 88)
    - Specifications (Box 30)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 30)
    - Slides (Box 30)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 94)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 33–35, Box 411)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 32, Box 35–37)
  - International Institute for the Study of Human Reproduction, Columbia University
    Job number: 6604
    - Correspondence (Box 127)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 127)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 137)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 140)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 139, Box 141)
  - Harlem River - Turtle Bay
    Job number: 6605x01
    Project type: Mixed Use Development
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 100–103, Box 541)
  - Irwin Union Bank and Trust Company, 1972
    Job number: 6606
    Project type: Bank
    - Correspondence (Box 578)
    - Specifications (Box 578)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 254)
  - Institute for Advanced Study, Princeton University
    Job number: 6701
    Job location: Princeton, NJ
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 343)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 244–246)
  - College Life Insurance Company of America Headquarters, 1971
    Job number: 6703
    Job location: Indianapolis, IN
    - Correspondence (Box 193)
    - Specifications (Box 193)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 193)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 192)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 194, Box 199–200)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 194–200)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 194, Box 197)
  - Orangery (Irwin Miller Pavilion)
    Job number: 68--
    Project type: Pavilion
    - Scrapbooks (Box 253)
  - Church Street Plaza
    Job number: 6804
    Project type: Public Plaza
    - Contracts (Box 144, Box 175)
  - Federal Reserve Bank of New York
    Job number: 6902
    - Correspondence (Box 39)
    - Contracts (Box 175)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 38)
    - Slides (Box 38)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 72)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 46–47, Box 243)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 48, Box 50–54, Box 242)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 142)
  - IBM Computer Technology Museum
    Job number: 6903
    Job location: Armonk, NY
    - Correspondence (Box 138)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 138)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 132)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 126)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 126)
  - United Nations Development Corporation, United Nations Plaza Office and Apartment/Hotel Phase I, 1975
    Job number: 6904
    Project type: Office Building
    - Scrapbooks (Box 106–108)
  - IBM Radio Tracer Laboratory, 1973
    Job number: 6905
    Job location: Yorktown, NY
    - Specifications (Box 218)
  - Cummins Engine Company Sub-Assembly Plant, Walesboro, 1973
    Job number: 7003 8406 9102 9507
    Job location: Walesboro, IN
    - Correspondence (Box 384–385, Box 412–413, Box 415–416)
    - Contracts (Box 385)
    - Specifications (Box 416)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 384)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 496)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 384, Box 396–398)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 398)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 396)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 395)
  - Worcester County National Bank, 1974
    Job number: 7005
    Job location: Worcester, MA
    - Correspondence (Box 273–274)
    - Specifications (Box 273)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 274)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 249)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 276–277, Box 279)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 275–279)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 275, Box 278)
  - Richardson-Vicks, Inc. Headquarters, 1974
    Job number: 7006
    Job location: Wilton, CT
    - Scrapbooks (Box 109)
  - Philadelphia Bicentennial
    Job number: 71--
    - Scrapbooks (Box 255)
  - Royal Bank of Canada, Office Complex Proposal
    Job number: 7101
    Job location: Toronto, Canada
    Project type: Bank/Office Building
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 144)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 155)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 143)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 143)
  - People's Bank, Indiana and Michigan Electric Company, Fort Wayne, Indiana, 1981
    Job number: 7201
    - Correspondence (Box 274, Box 291–292, Box 344, Box 467)
    - Specifications (Box 291–292, Box 517)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 274, Box 292)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 290)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 280–282)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 284–289, Box 293)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 283)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 283)
  - Fiat World Headquarters
    Job number: 7203
    Job location: Turin, Italy
    - Correspondence (Box 114)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 114)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 114)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 111, Box 113)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 113)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 112–113)
  - Denver Center for the Performing Arts, 1979
    Job number: 7301
    Job location: Denver, CO
    Project type: Performing Arts Center
    - Correspondence (Box 599–603)
    - Specifications (Box 601, Box 603, Box 609)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 607)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 607)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 604–609)
  - Kentucky Power Company Headquarters, 1978
    Job number: 7302
    Job location: Ashland, KY
    - Correspondence (Box 219–220, Box 222, Box 300, Box 344)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 219)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 221)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 240–241)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 223, Box 240–241)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 223)
  - University of Chicago, Law School, 1966
    Job number: 5504 6511 7303
    Job location: Chicago, IL
    - Correspondence (Box 218)
  - Deere & Company Headquarters - West Office Building, 1979
    Job number: 7501
    - Correspondence (Box 325, Box 343, Box 463)
    - Specifications (Box 325)
    - Photographs and Negatives (Box 325)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 252)
    - Drawings: Sketches (Box 331–332, Box 336)
    - Drawings: Schematic/Design Development (Box 334–336)
    - Drawings: Architectural/Structural (Box 335, Box 337)
    - Drawings: Site/Landscape (Box 331, Box 333, Box 336)
  - Texas Christian University, Moudy Visual Arts & Communications Building, 1981
    Job number: 7602
    Job location: Fort Worth, TX
    - Correspondence (Box 294–295)
    - Contracts (Box 295)